(Bernadette:)It's like I was excited
for a present and got socks.
(Stuart:)I don't understand how
that turns into
(Stuart:)the worst fight of your life.
(Sheldon:)I don't understand
what's wrong with socks.
(Penny:)To be fair,
we may have been on edge
(Penny:)because of the Christmas tree.
(Penny:)What happened
with the tree?
(Penny:)You do make a cute elf.
(Leonard:)Oh, yeah?
(Leonard:)And you thought Spock ears
were only good for Comic-Con.
(Penny:)Hey, hey, I just found a farm
(Penny:)where they let you chop down
your own tree.
(Leonard:)Oh cool, I'll be like
a pointy-eared Paul Bunyan.
(Leonard:)Stupid idea.
(Penny:)No, what's stupid is a physicist
(Penny:)who doesn't understand
when you swing an axe,
(Penny:)you don't let go.
(Leonard:)For the tenth time,
my mittens were slippery!